I'm Katherine Kwan, and I'm a developer advocate at Google. I started off by
working as an engineer on the Android apps team. I worked there for
three years on products like Google Play and Google Keep, the note taking app.
I'm continually blown away by what you can build on this platform, and
I'm particularly inspired by those apps that can truly improve people's lives.
When I meet people, they often tell me about their great app ideas. But
then they feel like they don't have the technical skills to actually build it.
And that's why I shifted over to developer relations so
I can help people like you really build something great. Throughout this course,
I'll be helping you implement your very first app.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> My name is Dan Gauthan. I've been a developer advocate at Google for
four years and I've worn a lot of hats here. My goal is to keep us on track to
make Sunshine, something that had some resemblance to a production quality app.
I'll introduce Android design patterns and principles. Many of which are often
missed by new Android developers. You'll learn to lean on the framework,
focusing on what makes your app unique instead of reinventing the wheel.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> I'm Rado Mya, and I've been a developer advocate at Google for five years.
I started working on Androids so long ago that back then there were no devices.
All we had to work with were an emulator, a beater SDK, and
an almost fanatical devotion to the platform. I'll be joining you from here,
my underground Android developer bunker, and my goal isn't to get you
up an running as quickly as possible. It's to teach you the context behind
the choices we'll make. And the best practices you need, to really understand
how to create great experiences specifically tailored to mobile devices. By
the time you finished this course you'll know more than just how to create yet
another app. You'll know how to build great apps that focus on the user.